Tanveer Najib

Personal Profile:

I am a reliable, enthusiastic and dedicated individual with the ability to adapt in any given task. I am an effective communicator who is able to organise a group in a workplace while keeping efficient in my own given task. I am a person who is always doing a job to the best of my ability, and I always aim to achieve a perfect result. I have been highly successful in meeting targets and have a driven work ethic. I am always ready to learn new skills and I have proven track records of attendance and punctuality. My previous experiences have improved my skills in computing and have given me a passion for working in a computer-based environment.

Skill and experience:

- The ability to work well as part of a team
- Creating documentation
- Staying organised in my tasks
- Sticking to a project

Technical Skills

Although this is a short list of technologies I have used, I am always open to learn more. Most of my open source projects are available on my <u>GitHub page</u>.

- C#
- Python
- Java
- JavaScript (incl. HTML & CSS)
- Object Oriented Programming
- Git

Voluntary Work:

- April 2013 present BASA
 Duties: Voluntary work organising sports events for the community.
 Keeping check of all sports inventory and scheduling the games within the event
- July 2017 July 2017 and Feb 2019 Feb 2019 **Zenith Marketing LTD**

Duties: Working in an office environment, inputting data and managing the company database.

Work Experience

September 2020 – July 2021 Weightron Bilanciai

Software Engineer: I was first line support for the first couple of months, and then eventually started developing systems for clients, as well as supporting them. I learnt the in-house programming language that is used for customer systems within one month. During the 11 months I learnt more about MSSQL and how to integrate it as a backend.

September 2021 – March 2022 GWD

Junior Software Developer: I worked at GWD as part of the 6 month long kickstart scheme. I spearheaded the development of multiple different internal company projects and worked with different departments. For example, I worked with the finance team to create a web form for employees to use whenever they make a purchase on behalf of the company. I also worked on a company statistics portal, in which I worked alongside upper management to ensure the best implementation.

Education:

2012-2018 Meadowhead Secondary School

Combined Science: 6/5

English Language: 6

History: 6

• Computer Science: 5

• Religious Studies: 5

Maths: 5

• English Literature: 4

• Art: 3

Resistant Materials: C

2018-2020 Meadowhead Sixth Form

• Computer Science: B

- English Language: B
- History: C

Interests and hobbies:

I am an outgoing person who enjoys socialising with my family and friends and meeting new people. I enjoy computer-based tasks and have a passion for programming – I have successfully released a group of software projects. In my spare time I like to improve my creativity by working on different Graphic Design projects and creating/contributing to open source software projects.

References

Available upon request_